Aditi Ray

Kolkata, West Bengal, India



imakeothersmile@gmail.com



8777831265



linkedin.com/in/thisisaditi

Summary

I am a freelance Web Designer, Web Developer, App Developer as well as a Graphic designer with nearly 2 years of experience along with professional certifications. I am a happy desktop always eager to learn new skills and explore them in a best possible way.

Key Skills:

- Programming Languages: Core JAVA, HTML, JavaScript, PHP and CSS
- Database Design: MySQL
- No Code Development: Webflow, Figma, Adalo, Canva
- Operating Systems: Windows, Linux
- Web Development, Front End Development, Android Development
- Graphic Design: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, InDesign, CorelDraw

You can check out my work at: aditiray.dorik.io

Check out My GitHub: https://github.com/iamaditiray

I adept at collaborating with dynamic teams to build high quality websites and identify opportunities to enhance the user experience. Need someone who will care about your success, communicate clearly, and anticipate options that minimize unwanted surprises?

I want to be that person for you. Let's get started!

Experience



Web Designer

Freelance

Feb 2021 - Present (2 years 2 months)

I am a Web developer, Web Dessigner and Graphic Designer specialising in high-quality Full-Stack Development and UI-UX designing.

Need someone who will care about your success, communicate clearly, and anticipate options that minimize unwanted surprises? I want to be that person for you. Let's get started!



Craphic Designer

DREAMS CLUES®#

Jun 2022 - Aug 2022 (3 months)

I have worked as a Graphic Designing Intern at Dreams' Clues for 2 months. I have applied for this post via Internshala. It was a very skillful as well conquering experience as I was introduced towards the industry requirements and also privileged to work on several diligent team projects along with the individual ones.



Chamela Helpdia Charitable Trust (CHCT)

May 2022 - Jun 2022 (2 months)

I have worked as a Designing Intern in Chamela Helpdia Charitable Trust for 1 month. I have applied for this post via Internshala. I was honored and privileged to be selected as their intern and so glad for having the opportunity to work with their well organized team. I came across a lot of experienced coworkers who helped me throughout in my growth during the internship period.

Education

University of Engineering & Management (UEM)

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Software Engineering Mar 2020 - Mar 2024

Holy Child Institute Girls' Higher Secondary School

Higher Secondary Education, Computer Science 2018 - 2020

Licenses & Certifications

Create a no-code responsive website with Webflow - Coursera RVB2DUD2EDAS

Build an App with Adalo - Coursera
TJHZ3ZZZ5UT9

Core Java - Internshala 53mi1qvpkwu

IBM Cybersecurity Analyst Specialization - Coursera

- Java Programming: Solving Problems with Software (with Honors) Coursera
- Introduction to Front-End Development Coursera
 V38S8DJHLQD2
- Programming with JavaScript Coursera
 32HWWXVLF47W
- Version Control Coursera
 GZ5UPGPHT5KZ

Skills

Version Control • Git • GitHub • Front-End Development • Computer Science • Social Media Marketing • Web Design • HTML Emails • Webflow • JavaScript